Guide to the John D. Wirth Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Original Accession, Accession ARCH-2002-288
  - Vice-Provost Files
    - Chrons, 1989 Jun (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Chrons, 1989 Jul (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Chrons, 1989 Aug (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Chrons, 1989 Sep (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Chrons, 1989 Oct (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Chrons, 1989 Nov (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Chrons, 1989 Dec (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Chrons, 1990 Jan (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Chrons, 1990 Feb (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Chrons, 1990 Mar (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Chrons, 1990 Apr (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Chrons, 1990 May (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Chrons, 1990 Jun (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Chrons, 1990 Jul (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Chrons, 1990 Aug (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Chrons, 1990 Sep (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Chrons, 1990 Oct (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - Chrons, 1990 Nov (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Chrons, 1990 Dec (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - Chrons, 1991 Jan (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - Chrons, 1991 Feb (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - Chrons, 1991 Mar (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - Chrons, 1991 Apr (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - Chrons, 1991 May (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - Chrons, 1991 Jun (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - Chrons, 1991 Jul (Box 13, Folder 40)
    - V. Provost floppy disks (Box 13, Folder 41)
    - Access to information (OMB) (Box 13, Folder 42)
    - ACSUS – Canadian Studies (Box 13, Folder 43)
    - Amazon rain forest (Box 13, Folder 44)
    - Americas Program (US/CAN/MEXICO) (Box 13, Folder 45)
    - Americas Program (Box 13, Folder 46)
    - African career development (Box 13, Folder 47)
    - Bing match (Box 13, Folder 48)
    - Bryce Wood Prize (Box 13, Folder 49)
    - CCC – copyright agreement (Box 13, Folder 50)
    - Canada (Box 13, Folder 51)
    - Canadian gift - Shultz (Box 13, Folder 52)
    - Canadian grants (Box 13, Folder 53)
    - Canadian films (Box 13, Folder 54)
    - Canadian Studies – UCB (Box 13, Folder 55)
    - Canadian Studies – Stanford (Box 13, Folder 56)
    - Canadian Federalism (Box 13, Folder 57)
    - Canada teaching material (Box 13, Folder 58)
    - Career Dept. Chairs (Box 13, Folder 59)
    - C-Lib (Box 13, Folder 60)
    - Chicano Studies Review (Box 13, Folder 61)
    - Central American Conference (Box 13, Folder 62)
    - CIV (Box 13, Folder 63)
    - Corey Prize (Box 13, Folder 64)
    - Drama – Theatre (Box 13, Folder 65)
    - School of Mines – Visiting Committee (Box 13, Folder 66)
    - Environment at Stanford Univ. [environmental studies] (Box 13, Folder 67)
    - Expense report receipts (Box 13, Folder 68)
    - Faculty seminar fundraising (Box 13, Folder 69)
    - Fort Burgwin [research center] (Box 13, Folder 70)
    - Fundamental Standards (Box 13, Folder 71)
    - Furniss lecture (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - John Gavin (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Gildred Chair (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Gulbenkian Foundation (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - History Department Undergraduate Curriculum Revision (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - History planning and new directions (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - University seminar (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - History Department study 1990 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Tom Holloway (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Canada – environment (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Jon Brown (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Colorado College – Donner (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Absurdities (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Alumni trips (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Steve Haber (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - The Honorable David C. Lam (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Calgary Conference May 1990 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - World history (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Institute of the Americas (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Jury Duty (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - David Kennedy (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Language Study (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - LAS/Americas Program (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - LAS/Mellon (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - LAS/Mellon (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - LA lunch (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - LAS Tinker Chair (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Latin America publishing (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Latin American fundraising (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Latin American Studies – Terry Karl (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Letters/Volunteers & Alumni (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - Long Range Planning Committee. Sub-committee on culture. Final report, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Luso-American Development Foundation (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - Ron McGerity (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - Mexus Review – UCB (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - Manufacturing Educ. endowment (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - Minority issues (Box 14, Folder 37)
    - Montage proposal (Box 14, Folder 38)
    - PFCCC – Jean Coblentz (Box 14, Folder 39)
    - Moss bequest (Box 14, Folder 40)
    - Multi-culturalism (Box 14, Folder 41)
    - NEH: Exemplary Humanities Programs for Adults (Box 14, Folder 42)
    - Consulting (Box 14, Folder 43)
    - OMB Circular A-130 (Box 14, Folder 44)
    - LA [Latin American] campus – debt equity (Box 14, Folder 45)
    - Overseas Studies (Box 14, Folder 46)
    - Development – Overseas Studies (Box 14, Folder 47)
    - Public History / IPS (Box 14, Folder 48)
    - Public Service Center Annual Report 1987-88 (Box 14, Folder 49)
    - Public Service Center (Box 14, Folder 50)
    - Public Service Center (Box 14, Folder 51)
    - Stanford in Washington (Box 14, Folder 52)
    - Remo Vescia (Box 14, Folder 53)
    - Requests for Funding Approval (Box 14, Folder 54)
    - Staffing Questions (Box 14, Folder 55)
    - Teaching Fellows (Box 14, Folder 56)
    - TEW/JDW talk [Timothy E. Wirth] (Box 14, Folder 57)
    - Tim Wirth seminar 6/89 (Box 14, Folder 58)
    - TEW lecture (Box 14, Folder 59)
    - Tinker Chair (Box 14, Folder 60)
    - Tinker Foundation (Box 14, Folder 61)
    - UNM (Box 14, Folder 62)
    - Van Damm (Box 14, Folder 63)
    - Webb course & philanthropy (Box 14, Folder 64)
    - Western history – Bill Lane (Box 14, Folder 65)
    - Western Culture debate, Spring 1986 (Box 14, Folder 66)
    - Western history – articles (Box 14, Folder 67)
    - Western Studies (Box 14, Folder 68)
    - SUP – Western Encyclopedia (Box 14, Folder 69)
    - Wirth Bros. – OOD (Box 14, Folder 70)
    - Fred Woerner (Box 14, Folder 71)
    - Scott Anderson (Box 14, Folder 72)
    - Proposed theater building (Box 14, Folder 73)
    - C-GS Report 1986-7 (Box 14, Folder 74)
    - Modernism Colloq. S & P (Box 14, Folder 75)
    - Americas Program (Box 14, Folder 76)
    - Policies (appointments, leaves, etc.) (Box 14, Folder 77)
    - Assorted papers and publications on LA by others (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Law and Society, Brazil (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Francisco Clementino de San Tiago Dantas, "Legal Education and the Brazilian Crisis," 1973 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Tom Heller (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - History 479, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - History 283/383, Spring 1981 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - McCann's manuscript [Frank McCann, with comments by Wirth, 1979] (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - History 180b, final exam, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Robert Levine, "Sport and Society: The Case of Brazilian Futebol" (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Assorted publications on Brazil (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Norman Gall, Letter from Rondonia: A Report on the Brazilian Frontier, 1977 [typescript – pre-publication form] (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Richard M. Morse, "The Urban Development of Colonial Spanish America" and F. M. Cardosa, "Development under Fire" (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Assorted publications on LA (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Center business (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence and documents (from same envelope as "center business" folder) (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Robert W. Shirley, "The Judicial System of Sao Paulo State, Brazil," 1973 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - LAS seminar (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - LAS core seminar reading (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Assorted papers by others (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Crime and punishment in Brazil (History 482) (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Crime and punishment in Latin America (History 381) 1977 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Unlabelled [more re Crime and punishment in Latin America] (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - History 281 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Assorted source materials (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - [LAS squatters (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Core seminar 1977-78 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Darrell E. Levi, "The Modernizing Family in Brazil, " 1973 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Roderick & Jean Barman, "The Role of the Law Graduate in the Political Elite of Imperial Brazil" 1976 (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Michael L. Conniff, "The Tenentes in Power," (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Peter Fry, "Two Religious Movements: Protestantism and Umbanda" 1978 (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - When the Guatemalans Were Blown Sky High (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - Unsorted miscellany – some class materials, some notes (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - John D. Wirth, "The Alberta-California Pipeline Project" 1989 (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - Robert Shirley, "Legal Institutions and Early Industrial Growth Manchester/Sao Paulo" [legal folder – sits on top of other folders] (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - Evelina Dagnino, "National Unity and Civil Society" 1985 – ch. 4 of her dissertation [legal folder – sits on top of other folders] (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Student and Colleague Files
    Some material may be restricted/confidential
    - Letter to G. W. Merkx, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence 1994 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Fellowship/dissertation proposals – recent (1974-1981) (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Thomas Whigham 1984 (letter and manuscript) (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Bob Slenes 1984-85 (correspondence and manuscript) (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Johan Van den Bossche (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Chuck Bergquist (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Victor Filler (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Peter Blasenheim (1973-81) (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - John H. Galey (1972-83) (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Michael L. Conniff (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Michael L. Conniff (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Michael L. Conniff – chapters (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Michael L. Conniff (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Letter from "Michael", Lima, Peru, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - George W. Schuyler (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Peter Blasenheim (1969-73) (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Rebecca Baird (Bergstresser) (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - E. Wilson (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Pat Stea (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Victor Filler (1976-71) (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Rolando Perez (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Conniff, Michael Lee (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Joseph F. Towner (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - John Wheat (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Michael Jimenez (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - John Wibel (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Robert Slenes (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Stuart L. Wagner (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Charles O'Neil (Texas) (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Stephen Jay Stein (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Timothy Harding (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Assorted students (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Nathan Laks (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - Jesse de la Cruz (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - Prof. Oneyr F. Baranda (Box 16, Folder 36)
    - Nathan E. Laks (Box 16, Folder 37)
    - Mike Conniff (Box 16, Folder 38)
    - Requests for Library purchases (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - Octavio Ianni (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - Euclydes Aranha Netto (Box 16, Folder 41)
    - Judith Tendler (Box 16, Folder 42)
    - Amazonas - professor (Box 16, Folder 43)
    - Rick Walter (Box 16, Folder 44)
    - Ralph della Cava (Box 16, Folder 45)
    - Gabriel Cohn (Box 16, Folder 46)
    - Richard Graham (Box 16, Folder 47)
    - Peter H. Smith (Box 16, Folder 48)
    - Thomas Skidmore (Box 16, Folder 49)
    - Fred Bowser (Box 16, Folder 50)
    - Don Ramos (Box 16, Folder 51)
    - Falcoff, Mike - Oregon (Box 16, Folder 52)
    - James Lauer (Box 16, Folder 53)
    - Joseph Love 1971 (Box 16, Folder 54)
    - Jeff Adelman (Box 16, Folder 55)
    - R. K. (Kim) Stevens (Box 16, Folder 56)
    - George Seay (Box 16, Folder 57)
  - Guide to the Study of Brazil in the United States, 1945-2000; Paulo Roberto de Almeida, Marshall C. Eakin, editors. Brazilian Embassy, Washington December 2000 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - H. S. Ferns, "A Question of Debt; The Baring Crisis in Anglo-Argentine History 1890-1896"; with letter requesting publication 1989 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Typescript: "Latin American Oil Companies and the Politics of Energy" [edited by JDW; published 1985] (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Typescript: "The Prairies and the Pampas; Agrarian Policy in Canada and Argentina, 1880-1930" by Carl E. Solberg [published by SU Press in series edited by JDW and Thomas C. Heller] (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Typescript: "Minas Gerais in the Brazilian Federation 1889-1937" by JDW [published by SU Press in 1977] (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Jonathan Brown, "Oil and Revolution" – for evaluation July 1990 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Card files from book research (Box 18)
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-2003-178
  - Environmental Management (Box 1)
  - Pollution (Box 1)
  - Trasborder (Box 1)
  - ASEH (Box 1)
  - Key files – mostly correspondence, 1970s-1980s (Box 2-5)
    The tabs reflect communication with a deep cross-section of Latin Americanists at that time. These files were in 1987 house fire. Some very smoky manila folders have been replaced, but the order is that of JDW.
  - NAMI News (complete set) (Box 6)
  - JPAC (Box 6)
  - CEC (Box 6)
  - NAFTA (Box 6)
  - JDW writings and correspondence (Box 7)
  - no details available (Box 8-16)
  - Card files; research note cards (Box 17)
  - Card files; research note cards (Box 18)
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-2008-331
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-2010-083
  - LASA (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - JPAC Addresses (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - CEC (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - NY CFR: Correspondence, 1995 Jun 4-5 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - NY CFR: Notes, 1995 June 4-5 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - ENGO Correspondence, 1995 Feb 10-12 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - ENGO Address List, 1995 Feb 10-12 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Role of Engo, 1995 Feb 11-12 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Engo Publication, 1995 Feb 10-12 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Role of Engo, 1995 Feb 10-12 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Role of Engo, 1995 Feb 10-12 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - NAMI, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Reinventing North America, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - NAMI, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Board Packet, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Board Mtg, 1995 Jul 28 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Board Mtg, 1995 Dec 11 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Board Mtg, 1995 Jan 30 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Executive Committee Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - ASEH Panel, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - NAMI Correspondence, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Identities Book - From Binder (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Identities Book - II From Binder (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Identities (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Identities (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Identities Project (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - American Identity (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Identities - Revised Chapter 1993 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Introduction (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Identities Project (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Identities Project (1 of 2) (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Identities Project (1 of 2) (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Crombie (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Identities Book (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - NAFTA and Beyond (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Identities Book (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Sanchez, "Approaches to the Problem...", circa 1996 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - NAFTA & Beyond Conference, 1993 Nov 10 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - NAMI Annual Financial Statement, 1993 Sep (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Articles on Health Care (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Colloquium, 1993 Feb (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Agenda for Community (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - NAMI Forums and Co-conveners Correspondence and core groups (1 of 2), 1993 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - NAMI Forums and Co-conveners Correspondence and core groups (2 of 2), 1993 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - NAMI Correspondence, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - NAMI Correspondence, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - NAMI General Correspondence, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - NAMI General Correspondence, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - NAMI Correspondence, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - NAMI Correspondence, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - NAMI Correspondence, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - NAMI General Correspondence, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Interest Groups - Pro NAFTA (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - NAMI Workshop, Pre-Workshop, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - NAMI Correspondence, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - NAMI Misc. (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - John Wirth mail and messages 3/29-4/1, 1993 Mar-Apr (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - NAMI News #9 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - John Wirth mail and messages, 1993 Feb-Mar (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - John Wirth mail and messages, 1993 Jan (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - JDW mail, 1993 Feb (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - JDW (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - News Clippings, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Identities Collaborators, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - NAFTA Lobby (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Small Business Conference (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - ESTRAOA, "The Dynamics of Assimilation...", 1993 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - NAFTA - Course Material (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Los Caminos del Rio (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Phone numbers and addresses (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - NAMI Board Memoranda, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - T.R.A.D.E. Afta Nafta Forum, 1993 Jan 18 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - NAFTA - misc. (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Funding Leads (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Canadian Global Change Program (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - News Clippings, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Identity Book (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Bustamante (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Roemer (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Front and Introduction (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Trade/Integration (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - NAMI - misc. (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Co-conveners Correspondence core groups and general forum info., 1994 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - NAMI Board Memoranda, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - NY Exec. Committee Meeting Transcript (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - JDW Correspondence, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Photographs - Hist. and Natl. Indentity Colloq. (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - NAMI News (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Jim Gardner (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - 1998 News Clippings (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - NY Exec. Committee Meeting, 1994 Oct 21-22 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Board Meeting, 1994 Jun 17 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - NACEL - Dec (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Border Progress (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - JPAC Meeting - Business (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - MacArthur (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Vancouver (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - NY Meeting (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - NY Forum, 1994 Oct (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - NAMI - Free Trade (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - NAMI - Misc., 1994 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Richard Kiy, 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - NATV (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - NGO Conference (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - H & I Conference Notes, 1994 May 6-1994 May 8 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - H & I Conference Publication, 1994 May 6-1994 May 8 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - H & I Conference Correspondence, 1994 May 6-1994 May 8 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - H & I Conference Reading Materials, 1994 May 6-1994 May 8 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Econ - US (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - N.A. Envir. Coop. All, 1994 Mar 19-1994 Mar 25 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - N.A. Envir. Coop. Participants, 1994 Mar 19-1994 Mar 25 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - N.A. Envir. Coop. Papers (1 of 2), 1994 Mar 19-1994 Mar 25 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - N.A. Envir. Coop. Papers (2 of 2), 1994 Mar 19-1994 Mar 25 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Media & NAFTA Conference Papers, 1994 Mar 11-1994 Mar 13 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Media & NAFTA Conference Correspondence, 1994 Mar 11-1994 Mar 13 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - H & I Agenda, 1994 May 6-1994 May 8 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - H & I Bios, 1994 May 6-1994 May 8 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - JDW Talks/Articles for Nancy Wirth (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-2011-079
  This accession consists primarily of Worth's research files for Smelter Smoke in North America: The Politics of Transborder Pollution (Lawrence: University Press of Kansas, 2000).
  - Peru Smelter (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - ILO (Box 1, Folder 2-3)
  - Smelter Smoke (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - TRAIL, Cominco Notes, CNA and USNA (5x7 index cards in envelope) (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Mexican Archive (5x7 index cards in manilla envelope) (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Hal Rothman (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Kansas Press (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Steve Mumme (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - [unlabeled] (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Lynne Snyder (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Smelter Concepts (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - James Allum (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Elites (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Bibliography - documents (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Smelter manuscript - Swain leads (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Requests for documents and information (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - [loose papers] (Box 1)
  - [unlabeled folder] (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - USDA/fumes/NRC (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Canadian National Archives - trail (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - U.S Government Documents and Actions (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - [unlabeled folders with a few loose papers interspersed] (Box 1, Folder 22-25)
  - [loose photocopies] (Box 1)
  - Fitzhugh Green Papers (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - U.S./Canaca [illegible] in 1930s (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Mexico/Trail link, 1930s (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - 1930s - [illegible] invisible injury (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Hedgcock Maps (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Reginald Dean (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - USDA and other smelter cases (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - U.S. Bureau of Mines (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Robert Swain (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Key articles (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - 1949 symposium: Swain, Katz, Hill (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - 1937 hearings / 1929 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Requests for info/addresses (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Charts, photos, dups (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Soils and Air (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Cost of Investigations (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - READ/Skelton (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Smelter Fumes: Knight Diary (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Water/slag pollution (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Health Issue (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Canadian Research (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Skelton Papers (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - USDA Publications Strategy (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Companies' Research (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Trail Management (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Canadian Farmers (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Cumulative Injury / Invisible Injury (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Monitoring Emissions (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - John Read (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Settlement to U.S. Claimants (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Assessing Damage (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Raftis bio info (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - John T. Raftis (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Metzger and Companies (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - North American Linkages (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Northport Area - settlers' claims (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Northport and area - economic data and smoke damage (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Trail - Flow of Diplomatic Business (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Lon Johnson (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Cooperation? (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Congressmen/Senators (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Washington/British Columbia (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - IJC (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Trail Arbitral Commission (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Diplomacy: American (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Diplomacy: Canadian (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - 1937-1938 Arbitration (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Taddy hall Thesis (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - [Arbitration] (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Regime Placed on Trail, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Air Treaty with Canada (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Farmers (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Trail Production (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Trail - Corporate Strategy (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Photos: USBM; Plant Ind RG54 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Newspapers (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Mining - Can and Northport Area (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Trail Community (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - British Columbia (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Smelters and Litigation (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Fertilizer/acid plant (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Washington State (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Ducktown (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Dick Camp xerox (Box 3)
  - Kamp documents and clippings (Box 3)
  - Copper Mines, U.S. and Mexico (Box 3)
  - Skinner [USDA personnel records] (Box 3)